(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Lily was playing a computer game.
Random people online are grouped in fives.
They all play against each other.
You can also talk to the other players.
Lily noticed that someone had sent her a
message.
She clicked on the inbox.
It was from someone she did not know.
The person said, hi.
It was a guy.
She was deciding whether or not to reply.
Her mom always said not to talk to
strangers, but her dad said every friend was
once a stranger.
She said hi.
The guy asked where she was from.
She told him she was from Los Angeles.
He was from there too.
They turned out to be from the same
math class.